module.exports=[
    {
        "question":" Which of the following option leads to the portability and security of Java?",
        "option1":"Bytecode is executed by JVM",
        "option2":"The applet makes the Java code secure and portable",
        "option3":"Use of exception handling",
        "option4":"Dynamic binding between objects",
        "correctans":1,
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is not a Java features?",
        "option1":"Dynamic",
        "option2":"Architecture Neutral",
        "option3":"Use of pointers",
        "option4":"Object-oriented",
        "correctans":3,
    },
    {
        "question":"The \u0021 article referred to as a",
        "option1":"Unicode escape sequence",
        "option2":"Octal escape",
        "option3":"Hexadecimal",
        "option4":"Line feed",
        "correctans":1,
    },
    {
        "question":" _____ is used to find and fix bugs in the Java programs.",
        "option1":"JVM",
        "option2":"JRE",
        "option3":"JDK",
        "option4":"JDB",
        "correctans":4,
    },
    {
        "question":"In which process, a local variable has the same name as one of the instance variables?",
        "option1":"Serialization",
        "option2":"Variable Shadowing",
        "option3":"Abstraction",
        "option4":"Multi-threading",
        "correctans":2,
    },
    {
        "question":" What is the return type of the hashCode() method in the Object class?",
        "option1":"Object",
        "option2":"int",
        "option3":"long",
        "option4":"void",
        "correctans":2,
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is a valid long literal?",
        "option1":"ABH8097",
        "option2":"L990023",
        "option3":"904423",
        "option4":"0xnf029L",
        "correctans":4,
    },
    {
        "question":"What does the expression float a = 35 / 0 return?",
        "option1":"0",
        "option2":"Not a Number",
        "option3":"Infinity",
        "option4":"Run time Exception",
        "correctans":3,
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following tool is used to generate API documentation in HTML format from doc comments in source code?",
        "option1":"javap tool",
        "option2":"javaw command",
        "option3":"Javadoc tool",
        "option4":"javah command",
        "correctans":3,
    },
    {
        "question":" Which method of the Class.class is used to determine the name of a class represented by the class object as a String?",
        "option1":"getClass()",
        "option2":"intern()",
        "option3":"getName()",
        "option4":"toString()",
        "correctans":3,
    }
  ];
  